(Howard:)If anything goes down,
(Howard:)we just put Koothrappali
in the driver's seat
(Howard:)and slap a sombrero
on his head.
(Raj:)Dude, how many races can you
offend in a single breath?
(Amy:)I don't know.
(Howard:)Have you watched
the Olympics with me?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, can you believe
that we're driving in a van
(Leonard:)that was owned by one of
the greatest scientific minds
(Leonard:)of the 20th century?
(Leonard:)It's like the Batmobile.
(Leonard:)If Batman was real
(Leonard:)and a physicist
(Leonard:)and his car wasn't cool.
(Sheldon:)It is extraordinary.
(Raj:)Perhaps some of his mojo
will rub off on us.
(Raj:)Maybe between this
and his beach house,
(Raj:)we will be inspired
to greatness.
(Sheldon:)I usually don't put too much
stock in charms and talismans.
(Sheldon:)However, even I must admit
(Sheldon:)feeling Richard Feynman's
(Sheldon:)butt dent cupping
my own bottom...
(Sheldon:)that does get
the creative juices flowing.
(Howard:)Hey, I have to return this van.
(Howard:)Keep your creative juices
in your pants.
(bang and hiss)
(Sheldon:)What was that?
I think it's a tire.